My name is marcel and...
我叫马塞尔
oh...no...that's not the first time I've done that
啊..不...我不是第一次干这个
My name is marcel and I'm partially a shell
我叫马塞尔，我身体的一部分是贝壳
as you can see on my wallet but...
就像你在我钱包上看到的那样...但是...
I also have shoes and...hem...a face...so
我也有鞋子和...一张脸..
I like that about myself and I like myself
我喜欢自己这个样子，我喜欢自己
and I have a lot of other great qualities as well
我也有其他的很多优秀品质
I know how it looks in here but it's not always so messy
我知道这儿看起来乱糟糟但平常不是酱的
but I didn't know that you were gonna have a camera and...
我不知道你要拍我
I wish that you had said that you were gonna be here today
如果你告诉了我你今天要来就好了
coz I didn't, I didn't clean up
因为我没有打扫卫生
I invited some friends from Upstates,XXXX
我请了一些北部朋友来玩(有两个词没听出来⊙?⊙)
so...that's...well...that's just how it looks right now
所以...好吧这里就是这么乱糟糟了
-guess what I wear as a hat
-what
猜猜我的帽子是啥
a lentil
一颗小扁豆
one time I nibbled on a piece of cheese
我有一次咬了一口芝士
and my cholesterol went up to 900...
然后我的胆固醇升到了900...
-guess what I use to tie my skis to my car
-what
猜猜我用什么来将滑雪板绑在我的车上
a hair
一根头发
-guess what my skis are
-what
猜猜我的滑雪板是什么
toenails from a man
一个男人的脚趾甲
-you want to see my talk on the phone
-sure
你想看我聊电话吗？
hello, this is me
what?yeah
yeah...well I could do it...yes
我可以
what? It would be my pleasure
这是我的荣幸
I did, I did
对，对
in fact I forgot to write a note
实际上我忘记记笔记了
thank you so much
谢谢您的来电
guess what I use as a beanbag chair
猜猜我用什么来做有豆袋坐垫的椅子
what
a raisin
一颗葡萄干
guess what I do for an adventure
猜猜我去冒险都干些什么
what
I'll hang-glide on a Dorito
我在玉米片上悬挂式滑翔
guess what I use as a pen
猜猜我用什么来做钢笔
what
I use a pen but it takes the whole family
我用钢笔做钢笔，但每次都需要整个家庭来帮我
I'm afraid to drink soda
我害怕喝汽水
because I'm afraid the bubbles would make me
float up onto the ceiling...
因为我怕泡泡会使我浮上天花板...
ok...err...
my one regret in life is that I will never have a dog
我人生一大遗憾就是我不能养狗
but sometimes I tie a hair to a piece of lint
但我有时候在一块小碎布上绑一跟头发
I love you, come with me
我可爱你了，跟我来吧
and I drag it around
然后带它溜来溜去
come
来吧
come, come onnnnnn
来来来吧
one time I smelled a smell from an old tennis sneaker
我有一次闻到一股从一只旧网球鞋飘来的臭味
and it knocked me right out
然后我马上被熏晕了
one time I looked at a diamond and it gave me a sunburn
我有次看了看一颗钻石然后被晒伤了
His name is Allen
他的名字是亚伦
guess where I found him
猜猜我在哪儿找到他
where
under a tooth
一只牙齿下面
well, you know what they say
你懂的，人们常说
what
lint is a shell's best friend
小碎布是贝壳的好朋友（字幕君：就如狗是人类的好朋友）
do you want to watch me try to lift this?
你想看我举起这个吗？
sure
alright
好吧
no, I can't
不，我不行
I can't lift anything up at all
我啥都举不起来
sometimes people say that my head is too big for my body
有时候人们说我的头对于我身体来说太大了
and then I say "compared to what?"
然后我说“那得看跟什么比较”
My brother once got in a fight with someone else
有一次我兄弟跟别人打架
and guess how he killed him
猜猜他怎样杀死他的
how
he impaled him on a brush
他把他刺在刷子上
sounds very violent
好暴力哦
we won't fight unless we are provoked
如果不是被惹毛，我们不打架的
come here
I love you~
come~here~